When the law put up the money The Bounty Hunter put on his guns!
The Bounty Hunter is a western, action film directed by André de Toth.
A year after a violent train robbery the Pinkerton detective agency
hires a bounty hunter to find the three remaining killers.
He tracks them to Twin Forks but has no clue to their identity.
Tensions surface as just his presence in town acts as a catalyst.
Jim Kipp / James Collins, played by Randolph Scott.
Julie Spencer, played by Dolores Dorn.
Alice Williams, played by Marie Windsor.
Sheriff Brand, played by Howard Petrie.
Dr. R.L. Spencer, played by Harry Antrim.
George Williams, played by Robert Keys.
The Bounty Hunter is a 1954 American western film directed by Andre DeToth
and starring Randolph Scott, Marie Windsor and Dolores Dorn.
It was the last of six Randolph Scott westerns with DeToth and the
first film to feature a bounty hunter as its hero.
It was released by Warner Bros.
It was filmed in 3-D but released in standard format, though
a 3-D print exists in the Warner archives.
Stock footage from the 1952 film Carson City is
used at the beginning of the film.
Portions of the film were shot on location in California
at Red Rock Canyon and the Mojave Desert.
The tone is dark.